▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 第三轮
兹维列夫 7-6(4) 7-6(6) 阿特马内 · 赛后场上采访
Sasha, congratulations,
萨沙 恭喜你
that was a lot of fun,
这场打得很过瘾
a lot of respect between the two of you.
你们俩之间充满了尊重
How high
水平有多高
was the level you both reached tonight?
你们今晚打出的水平？
Yeah, really good.
是啊 真的很棒
I think really a step up from the first match
感觉比上一场更上一个档次
and he played amazing tennis,
他今天打得非常出色
incredibly aggressive, served unbelievable,
打得极具侵略性 发球也很凶
hit forehands all over the court.
正手打得满场飞
So yeah, definitely happy
所以 我很高兴
to be through in straight sets.
能直落两盘拿下
Your forehands had a lot of love this year,
你的正手今年一直很受关注
understandably,
这也不难理解
but it was the trusty back end
但今天关键时刻
that got it done there at the end.
帮你赢下的是那记反手
Well, I think it was just the shot
我觉得那只是那一刻的一拍
in that moment, but overall,
但总体来说
I think the heaviness and the speed
他的球又沉又快
of his shots is extremely high,
力量和速度都非常惊人
so it's definitely difficult
所以自己想主动进攻
to play aggressive yourself,
确实很难
but I'm happy that I managed in the end.
但我很高兴最后还是顶住了
You had to come off court in the second set.
第二盘你还中途下场了一趟
Can you explain why, are you okay?
说说是怎么回事 你没事吧？
I was just sweating,
就是出汗太多
I was making the whole court wet,
把整片场地都弄湿了
so the umpire told me to go change.
裁判让我去换身衣服
I mean, I was making the court so wet
我是说 场地被我弄得太湿了
that it was impossible to play.
都没法打了
Well done tonight.
今晚打得漂亮
Thank you.
谢谢